Finding aid to the Iva Dee Hiatt papers CA.MS.00281
Smith College Archives
Iva Dee Hiatt papers
1890-1980
Smith College Archives
Hiatt, Iva Dee, 1919-1980
CA.MS.00281
20.083 linear feet (18 containers)
Iva Dee Hiatt was Professor of Music at Smith College. The collection contains biographical material, course material, correspondence, performance material, and photographs.
Biographical / Historical
Iva Dee Hiatt was born in Indiana to John H. and Ester Miessner Lindley on Sept. 19, 1919, raised by a doctor before being adopted by Fred W. and Iva Lindley Hiatt, her aunt and uncle who lived in Berkeley in 1923. At the age of 16, Hiatt entered the University of California at Berkeley where she was an honor graduate, receiving a Masters in Music in 1941. She was a pupil of Ernest Bloch, Roger Sessions, Randall Thompson, Edward Lawton, Arthur Bliss, and Manfred Bukofzer, and was chosen first chorister of the University of California Chorus. By the time Hiatt was twenty one she had her pilot's license. Before coming to Smith in 1948, Hiatt taught at the San Francisco Conservatory of Music and the University of California Extension Division Music School, where she founded the Berkeley Chamber Singers in 1946-48 which premiered works by Aaron Copland and Stravinsky. Hiatt was the first woman to conduct the Orquestra Sinfonica Nacional of Mexico, the first woman and choral conductor to conduct a work for chorus and orchestra at Tanglewood, first woman to be an associate professor of music at Harvard Summer School, and the first woman to be the director of Choral Music at Smith College.
During Hiatt's 31 years as a teacher at Smith, she designed the choral system, created the Christmas Vespers program, and founded the Smith College Chamber Singers which earned numerous awards during its more than 20 concert tours abroad. She also took the Smith Glee club to Boston's Symphony Hall for Pops concerts, to Carnegie Hall, Town Hall, and Philharmonic Hall in New York City, and to Washington D.C to sing with the National Symphony Orchestra. Hiatt also established the tradition of student choral conducting that continues to provide early training for Smith conductors.
Hiatt was a teacher who "provided a distinguished model of purpose and achievement," according to one student. Her door was always open to students, sharing music and a belief in their capabilities. For all her accomplishments and efforts, Hiatt was awarded the Smith College Medal in May of 1979.
Among her other achievements, Hiatt was music director of the Cambridge Society for Early Music from 1965 to 1977, and founder and music director of the Choral Institute in Johnson, VT. She received an Honorary Degree, Doctor of Music, from New England Conservatory of Music in Boston and an Award for Outstanding Service for her assistance to the International Communication Agency of the State Department in advancing understanding and good will between people of the U.S and people of other countries.
Hiatt died at Cooley Dickinson Hospital on January 5, 1980 after a two year battle with A.L.S. (Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis).
Scope and Contents
The Iva Dee Hiatt papers contains biographical information about early and family life, diaries, correspondence, pilot logs, photographs, programs, newspaper articles and press releases, lectures, class notes, slides, school memorabilia, and trophies.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Iva Dee Hiatt Papers were donated over a period of time to the Smith College Archives from a variety of sources.
Related Materials
- MS 126 [Sophia Smith Collection], Judith Raskin papers, Smith Club Glee Club, phonograph, 1946-1947
- 10-inch 43, Smith College Chamber Singers and Glee Club, conducted by Iva Dee Hiatt, "Smith College Sings," 1952-1953
- CD 86, Smith College Glee Club and Chamber Singers, 1952-1953
- CD 55, Smith College Glee Club, "Alma Mater," 1953
- 12-inch 28-29, Smith College Choirs, 1955-1956
- 12. Tape Recording, 80. Special Days, "Christmas Vespers-Mozart's Regina Coeli," 1956
- 10-inch 42, 12-inch ?, Smith College Glee Club, Williams Glee Club (?), "Haydn: The Creation," 1957
- 12. Disc, Smith College Choir and Wesleyan University Glee Club, "Christmas Vespers," 1959
- 12-inch 37, Smith College Glee Club and Wesleyan University Glee Club, "A Service of Thanksgiving and Praise," 1967
- 12-inch 40, Smith College Glee Club and Choirs and Williams College Choral Society, "Christmas Vespers," 1969
- 12-inch 41, Smith College Glee Club and Harvard Glee Club, "Christmas Vespers," 1971
- 12-inch 42, Smith College Glee Club and Harvard Glee Club, "Christmas Vespers," 1972
- 12. TR, 52. Music department, Smith College Chamber Singers, "For Spectrum Group in the Alumnae House," 1973
- 12-inch 43-45, Smith College Glee Club and Chamber Orchestra, Amherst College Glee Club, "Bach: Mass in B Minor," 1974
- 12-inch 48, Smith College Glee Club and Harvard Glee Club, "Christmas Vespers," 1974
- 12. TR, 52. Music department, Smith College Choir and Lehigh University Glee Club, "Three Night Pieces," 1974
- 12-inch 49, Smith College Glee Club and Amherst Glee Club, "Christmas Vespers," 1975
- 12-inch 67-68, Smith College Chamber Singers, conducted by Iva Dee Hiatt, "The Smith College Chamber Singers on Tour," 1976
- 12-inch 50, Smith College Glee Club and Harvard Glee Club, "Christmas Vespers," 1976
- 12-inch 54, Smith College Glee Club and Cornell Glee Club, "Christmas Vespers," 1977
- 3-33.5 rpm LPs, 52. Music department, Smith College Choirs, "College Choirs at Christmas", 1977
- C064, Smith College Choir, University of Rochester Men's Glee Club and Fordham University Glee Club, "Brahms: Zigeunerlieder, Faure: Requiem," 1978
- 12-inch 55, Smith College Glee Club and Harvard Glee Club, "Christmas Vespers," 1978
- 12. TR, 52. Music department, Smith College Orchestra, Smith College Glee Club, and soloists, "Commencement Concert," 1979
- 12-inch 57, Smith College Glee Club and Choirs and Union College Glee Club, "Christmas Vespers," 1979
- C057, C456, 12. TR, Smith College Glee Club or Chorus, "Iva Dee Hiatt Memorial Concert," April 1980
- 17-inch 1-5, Smith College Glee Club and Princeton Chapel Choir, "Missa Oquam Gloriosum, Hosanna to the Son of David, Ave Vetum Corpus, Anse, O Ye Servants of God," n.d.
- Correspondence, Gail Cameron, 1952-55; undated (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Jill Conway, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Kayoko (Saito), 1963 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Seth Ulman, 1938-39 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Seth Ulman, 1943-44 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Seth Ulman, 1944 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Seth Ulman, 1945 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Seth Ulman, 1945 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Seth Ulman, 1945 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Seth Ulman, undated (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Lucrecia Weed, undated (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Richard K. Winslow, 1955-56; undated (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Johann (John), 1937; 1944; undated (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Jeanne, 1937; undated (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1938-45; undated (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1950-56 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1960-63 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1964-69 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1970 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1972 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1973 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1974 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1975; undated (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Crownfield (1 photograph), 1976 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1976 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1977 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Jan.-Nov. 1978 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Dec. 1978 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Jan.-Mar. 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Apr. 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, May 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, May 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Jun. 1-19, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, June 20-30, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Jul. 1-19, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Jul. 20-30, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Aug. 1-9, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Aug. 10-15, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Aug. 16-31, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Sept. 1-9, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Sept. 10-30, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General-Birthday Cards, Sept. 14, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Oct. 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Nov. 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Dec. 1-19, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, Dec. 20-31, 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General-Christmas cards, Dec. 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General-Christmas cards, Dec. 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General-Christmas cards, Dec. 1979 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, General, 1979?; undated (Box 2)
- Correspondence, General, 1979?; undated (Box 2)
- Correspondence, General, Jan. 1980 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, General, undated (Box 2)
- Correspondence, General, undated (Box 2)
- Correspondence, General, undated (Box 2)
- Correspondence, General, undated (Box 2)
- Correspondence, to Lucretia Weed, 1979 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, to Lucretia Weed in sympathy of Dee's death, Jan. 1980 (Box 2)
- Correspondence, to Fred Hiatt in sympathy of Dee's death, Jan. 1980 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-General (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Budget, 1976 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Calendar, 1976-77 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Clippings, 1960s (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Evaluations, Freshman Chorus, 1962 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.- Evaluations, Choirs, undated (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1944-45 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1946 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, Jan.-Oct. 1947 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, Nov.-Dec.1947 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1948 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1949 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1950-53 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1952-53 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1954 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1955 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence-U.S. Government, 1956 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1956-59 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence-from Randall Thompson, 1961 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1966-69 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1970-74 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence-Marshall Bartholomew, 1975 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1975-76 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence-Tour Information, 1975-76 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence, 1977-79 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence-Isobel P. Brooks Fund, 1974-77 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence-Misc., undated (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Correspondence-Scholarship Fund Concerts, 1950s (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Melody, Music 11, Nov. 9 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Lecture: Sistine Chapel Codices (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Seminar: Monteverdi (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Seminar: Renaissance, Secular Music (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Seminar: Renaissance, Spring 1975 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Special Studies 401A (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-on Josquin (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-1960s notes (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Course note, 1962; undated (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes, undated (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes, 1977; undated (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-"Almanac of the Seasons" (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Bach Cantata (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Bach: St. John Passion, notes, etc., 1969 (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Baroque Opera-Stradella, Scarlatti. (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Byrd (1543-1623) and Purcell (1659-1695) (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Brahms (1823-1897) (Box 2)
- Music Dept.-Teaching Notes-Roger Sessions (Box 2)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1949 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1950 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1951 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1951 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1951 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1951 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1952 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1952 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1952 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1953 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1953 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1953 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1954 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1954 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1954 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1954 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1955 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1955 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Misc., 1955 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1956 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1956 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1956 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1956 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1957 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings and Misc., 1957 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1958 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1958 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1958 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1958 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Misc., 1959 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1960 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Misc., 1960 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1961 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1961 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1961 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1961 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Misc., 1962 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1963 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1963 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Membership and Misc., 1963 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Misc., 1963 or 1964 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Misc. (with Amherst), 1963 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1965 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Memorandum, Schedules, 1965 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Instrumentalists (with Princeton), 1965 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs (with Wesleyan), 1966 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1967 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1968 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1968 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Reviews, 1968 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1968 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Misc., 1969 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1970 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1970 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs and Correspondence, 1971 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1972 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, Schedule, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 3)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1974 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1974 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence RE: Maggie Putnam, 1974-75 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1975 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1976 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-News Clippings, 1976 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1976 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Correspondence, 1977 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Programs, 1977 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Itinerary and Misc., 1977 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers Tour-Misc., undated (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-General and Misc. (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Budget, 1965 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Membership, 1965 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Radio Possibilities (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Scholarships, 1965 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Lincoln Center Festival, Sept. 1965 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Finances, 1968 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Budgets, 1968 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Scholarships, 1968 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Budget, 1973 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Routine Business, 1973-74 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Budget, 1976 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Members, Minutes, & Misc., 1976-77 (Box 4)
- Chamber Singers General-Fundraising, 1977 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-History, Summary of Miss Hiatt's Experience (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1940-41 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1948-49 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Memberships, 1950-51 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Singing with Williams College Glee Club, 1951-52 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Membership, Itinerary, Programs, etc., 1952-53 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-News Clippings, 1953 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Correspondence and Misc., 1953-54 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1953-54 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Members, Programs, Correspondence, etc., 1954-55 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-News Clippings, Press Book, 1954-55 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Misc. Concert Materials, 1955-56 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Membership, 1955-56 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Press Book, Publicity, 1955-56 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1956-57 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Misc., 1956-57 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1957-58 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Misc., 1957-58 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1958 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1959 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Spring Tour: Cleveland, Cincinnati, Hamilton, St. Louis, Pittsburg. 1 of 2, 1959 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Spring Tour: Cleveland, Cincinnati, Hamilton, St. Louis, Pittsburg. 2 of 2, 1959 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Scrapbook, 1958-59 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1960 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Press Book, 1959-60 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Scrapbook, 1959-60 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1960-61 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1960-61 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Tour Information, 1960-61 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Evaluations, 1961-62 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1961-62 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Misc., 1961-62 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1962-63 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Membership Lists, 1962-63 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Press Book, News Clippings, 1962-63 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Misc.-Programs, Schedules, etc., 1962-63 (Box 4)
- Glee Club-Six "Histories", 1962-63 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Correspondence of Officers, 1963-64 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Cabinet Meeting Minutes, 1963-64 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Membership Lists, 1963 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1963 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-News Clippings, Press Book, 1963-64 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1964-65 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Membership, Concerts, etc., 1964 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Cabinet Meeting Minutes, etc, 1964 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Press Book, 1964-65 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1965-66 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Membership Lists, 1965 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1965 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Tour with Wesleyan, 1966 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1966-67 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Washington D.C. Press Book, 1968 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, 1967-68 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1967-68 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1968-69 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Misc.-Notebook, etc., 1968-69 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Membership, Concert Materials, etc., 1969-70 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1970-71 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Publicity Notebook, News Clippings, 1970-71 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Membership and Misc., 1970-71 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Hatfield Tercentenary Celebration, 1970 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Membership, Daily Schedule, 1971-72 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Publicity, News Clippings, Programs, etc., 1972-73 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Year's Summary, Membership Lists, 1972-73 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Correspondence and Programs, 1972-73 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-News Clippings, 1972-73 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Summary of Year, 1973-74 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Programs, 1973-74 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Summary of Year, List of Officers, 1974-75 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-College Centennial, 1974-75 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Programs, Correspondence, 1974-75 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Misc.-Membership, Programs, etc., 1975-76 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Concerts-2nd Annual Women's Choral Festival, Strolling Concerts, 1976 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Misc., 1976-77 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Correspondence, Membership, 1977-78 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-News Clippings, Programs, 1977-78 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Summary of Year, Membership Lists, 1978-79 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Misc.-Letters, Programs, etc., 1978-79 (Box 5)
- Glee Club-Student Assistance (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1956 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1958 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1960 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1961 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1962 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1963 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert-Correspondence (originally labeled 1964), 1961-62 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1965 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1966 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1967 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1968 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1969 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1970 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1971 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1972 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1973 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1974 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1975 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1976 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1977 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, 1978 (Box 5)
- Pops Concert, undated (Box 5)
- Christmas Vespers-Programs from the 1940s (Box 6)
- Christmas Vespers-Programs from the 1950s (Box 6)
- Christmas Vespers-Programs from the 1960s (Box 6)
- Christmas Vespers-Programs from the 1970s (Box 6)
- Christmas Vespers-Procedural Info. Misc. Articles about (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: All-Smith Choir-Programs, 1952-55 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Alumnae Singers (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College Choir-General and Misc. (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College Choir-Lenten Vespers, 1956-59 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College Choir-Services of Thanksgiving and Praise, 1955-72 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College Choir-Bulletins from Guest Appearances at Various Churches, 1955-59 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College Choir-Misc. Concerts, 1956-63 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College Choir Competition and Choral Concert, 1952-75 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College-Random Singing Groups, 1954-55 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College Misc. Groups, 1953-77 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College Choral Singers, 1950s (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Budget and Finances, 1965 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Form Letters, Appeals for Money, 1953-56 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith College Singers, 1957 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith-Wesleyan Concert Choir, Mexican Tour, 1962 (Box 6)
- Misc. Vocal Groups: Smith-Wesleyan Concert Choir, 1963 (Box 6)
- Repertory: Bach B-Minor Mass, 1974 (Box 6)
- Repertory: Bach's Matthew Passion, 1973 (Box 6)
- Repertory: Chant Ideas (Box 6)
- Repertory: Christmas Programs-Non Smith (Box 6)
- Repertory: Choral Music Catalogs (Box 6)
- Repertory: Choral Music for Women's Voices-Lists (Box 6)
- Repertory: Dido and Aeneas, 1971 (Box 6)
- Repertory: Dream Thing on Biblical Episodes for Smith College Chamber Singers (Box 6)
- Repertory: Early Dance (Box 6)
- Repertory: Early Music 1 of 2 (Box 6)
- Repertory: Early Music 1 of 2 (Box 6)
- Repertory: Early Music (Machaut, Fauvel) (Box 6)
- Repertory: Electronic Music (Box 6)
- Repertory: English Music Festival, 1960s (Box 6)
- Repertory: Graphic Ideas (Box 6)
- Repertory: Hayden-Masses, Operas (Box 6)
- Repertory: Ideas from Concerts, Lists (Box 6)
- Repertory: Instruments (Box 6)
- Repertory: Italian Madrigal-Luca Marenzio (1553-1599) (Box 6)
- Repertory: Magnificat from Sacre Symphoniae (Box 6)
- Repertory: Medieval Liturgical Drama (Box 6)
- Repertory: Medieval Material (Box 6)
- Repertory: Misc. (Box 6)
- Repertory: Monteverdi (Box 6)
- Repertory: Monrovian and Early Am. Music (Box 7)
- Repertory: Mozart Masses (Box 7)
- Repertory: Poulenic and Faure (Box 7)
- Repertory: Renaissance-Ceremonial Music in Venice (Box 7)
- Repertory: Renaissance: Art/Music (How to analyze Renaissance Music) (Box 7)
- Repertory: St. Martin and Acquitanian Repertory (Box 7)
- Repertory: Heinrch Schutz (1585-1672) (Box 7)
- Repertory: The Smith-Hamilton Dunstable Singers, 1963 (Box 7)
- Repertory: Stravinsky (1882-1971) (Box 7)
- Repertory: 20th Century Choral Works (Box 7)